module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What early 90s Microsoft software program was a CD-ROM of a digital multimedia encyclopedia?', 
      a: 'Real Player', 
      b: 'Corel',
      c: 'Mosaic',
      d: 'Encarta',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which narrow-edged tooth is used for cutting and gnawing?', 
      a: 'Incisor', 
      b: 'Molar',
      c: 'Canine',
      d: 'Premolar',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'In the classic board game Candy Land, what is the name of the king who rules the Candy Castle?', 
      a: 'King Jolly', 
      b: 'King Gumdrop',
      c: 'King Kandy',
      d: 'King Licorice',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is the author of the vampire romance series "Twilight"?', 
      a: 'Karen Kingsbury', 
      b: 'Francine Rivers',
      c: 'Stephenie Meyer',
      d: 'Nicholas Sparks',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which material is attracted to magnets?', 
      a: 'Iron', 
      b: 'Copper',
      c: 'Aluminum',
      d: 'Brass',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What electronics retailer exclusively sold "Tandy" computers during the mid-1980s?', 
      a: 'PC Richard', 
      b: 'Radio Shack',
      c: 'Comp USA',
      d: 'Circuit City',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of a trait that is expressed whenever it is present in DNA?', 
      a: 'Recessive', 
      b: 'Expressive',
      c: 'Dominant',
      d: 'Inheritive',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Holden Caulfield is the main character of which novel?', 
      a: 'To Kill A Mockingbird', 
      b: 'Catcher in the Rye',
      c: 'The Great Gatsby',
      d: 'Lord of the Flies',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the capital city of Canada?', 
      a: 'Ottawa', 
      b: 'Toronto',
      c: 'Montreal',
      d: 'Vancouver',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: '#000000 is the hex code for what color?', 
      a: 'Red', 
      b: 'White',
      c: 'Black',
      d: 'Blue',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};